http://www.compassionatecommunication.org/terms-and-conditions/

Terms and Conditions
Welcome to our Privacy Policy
— Your privacy is critically important to us.
Compassionate Commuication is located at:
Compassionate Commuication
It is Compassionate Commuication’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to www.compassionatecommunication.org/ (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “www.compassionatecommunication.org/”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
– Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Compassionate Commuication collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Compassionate Commuication’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Compassionate Commuication’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Compassionate Commuication may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Compassionate Commuication also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on http://www.compassionatecommunication.org/ blog posts. Compassionate Commuication only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
– Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Compassionate Commuication’s websites choose to interact with Compassionate Commuication in ways that require Compassionate Commuication to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Compassionate Commuication gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at http://www.compassionatecommunication.org/ to provide a username and email address.
– Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
– Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Compassionate Commuication and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
– Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
– Www.compassionatecommunication.org/ uses Google AdWords for remarketing
Www.compassionatecommunication.org/ uses the remarketing services to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
– Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Compassionate Commuication discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Compassionate Commuication’s behalf or to provide services available at Compassionate Commuication’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Compassionate Commuication’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Compassionate Commuication will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Compassionate Commuication discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Compassionate Commuication believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Compassionate Commuication, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of http://www.compassionatecommunication.org/ and have supplied your email address, Compassionate Commuication may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Compassionate Commuication and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Compassionate Commuication takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
– Aggregated Statistics
Compassionate Commuication may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Compassionate Commuication may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Compassionate Commuication does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
– Affiliate Disclosure
This site uses affiliate links and does earn a commission from certain links. This does not affect your purchases or the price you may pay.
– Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Compassionate Commuication uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Compassionate Commuication uses cookies to help Compassionate Commuication identify and track visitors, their usage of http://www.compassionatecommunication.org/, and their website access preferences. Compassionate Commuication visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Compassionate Commuication’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Compassionate Commuication’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Compassionate Commuication’s use of cookies.
– E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Compassionate Commuication – by purchasing Compassionate Commuication’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Compassionate Commuication collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Compassionate Commuication. Compassionate Commuication does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
– Business Transfers
If Compassionate Commuication, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Compassionate Commuication goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Compassionate Commuication may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Compassionate Commuication may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Compassionate Commuication’s sole discretion. Compassionate Commuication encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
–
– Credit & Contact Information
This privacy policy was created at https://termsandconditionstemplate.com/privacy-policy-generator/. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via or phone.
Search for:
Recent Comments Archives
Categories
No categories
Compassionate CommunicationAn error has occurred, which probably means the feed is down. Try again later.
